<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>all events</title><link>https://etsy.com/</link><description>New in etsy</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 02:12:47 -0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Nursery Wall Decal with Forest Animals</title><link>https://www.etsy.com/listing/156654709/nursery-wall-decal-with-forest-animals?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api</link><description>For more of our designs and products please visit us at https://www.etsy.com/shop/DesignsbyDelia09



♥♥♥♥ Included ♥♥♥♥

1 Deer - 25&amp;quot; Tall by 16&amp;quot; wide
2 Squirrels
2 Bunnies
4 Birds
Directions for applying your decals



♥♥♥♥ Colors ♥♥♥♥♥

In the &amp;#39;message to seller&amp;#39; section at checkout please indicate the colors you would like from the color chart posted above. You may select the following:

Color for the deer
Color for the squirrels
Color for the bunnies
Color for the birds

If no colors are selected the colors shown will be sent.



♥♥♥♥ Orientation ♥♥♥♥

If you would like this to face the opposite direction, please leave us a note saying &amp;quot;REVERSE&amp;quot; in the the &amp;#39;message to seller&amp;#39; section at checkout.



♥♥♥♥Customize♥♥♥♥

If you would like a different size or if you would like to incorporate or combine items from our other listings please convo us and we can create a custom order for you. 



♥♥♥♥ Materials ♥♥♥♥

Our decals are made from high quality indoor vinyl designed to be removed (but not re-used) without leaving any residue. The have a beautiful matte finish which gives the decal a painted on look.



♥♥♥♥ Replacements ♥♥♥♥

Our decals come in separate pieces so that may be arranged in whatever order you prefer. If for some reason a piece is damaged during installation, please contact us for a replacement.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">no</guid></item><item><title>Vintage Homco Squirrel Figurine, Masterpiece Porcelain Figurine, Squirrel in a Log Figure, Vintage Porcelain Figurine</title><link>https://www.etsy.com/listing/679525037/vintage-homco-squirrel-figurine?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api</link><description>Vintage Homco Squirrel Figurine, Masterpiece Porcelain Figurine, Squirrel in a Log Figure, Vintage Porcelain Figurine

Beautiful Homco porcelain figurine of gray squirrel in a log. Colorful and detailed, not to mention adorable.

This little guy is in excellent condition; no flaws detected. Made in Mexico, c1986, Masterpiece Porcelain, and signed by artist Mizuno. 

Measures 5.25&amp;quot; in length, and about 4.25&amp;quot; in height. 

Thanks for looking.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">no</guid></item><item><title>Forest Green Hoodie with full colour Pheasant Embroidery exclusively designed by Devon Wild.</title><link>https://www.etsy.com/listing/665685110/forest-green-hoodie-with-full-colour?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api</link><description>The Forest Green cosy Hoodie by Devon Wild has a full colour embroidered pheasant which is a must have for your cold weather wardrobe.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">no</guid></item><item><title>6-48 Supply Wooden Buttons Tree Buttons Wood Buttons - Sewing Buttons 20mm - Tree of Life Buttons Brown - Buttons Forest Woodland Buttons</title><link>https://www.etsy.com/listing/518076602/6-48-supply-wooden-buttons-tree-buttons?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api</link><description>TREE OF LIFE BUTTONS

These natural wood buttons have been engraved with the tree of life.  They are both beautiful and practical.  Perfect for adding stylish detail to all kinds of project.

Material:	Wood
Size:  20mm
Holes:  2
Quantity: 12 or 24 Buttons (please select from drop down list)

Why not check out more of our buttons? http://etsy.me/2BasjDa</description><guid isPermaLink="false">no</guid></item><item><title>white birch wood candle holder - carved heart &amp; initials, personalized candle, anniversary gift, 5 years anniversary gift, rustic candle</title><link>https://www.etsy.com/listing/77157256/white-birch-wood-candle-holder-carved?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api</link><description>Personalized Maine birch candle holder


Details:
- Approximately 3&amp;quot; in diameter and 4&amp;quot; in tall. 1.75&amp;quot; diameter hole for a tea light
- This natural product will vary in shape and size
- Natural birch branch
- Comes with a tea light


Explore our shop!
https://www.etsy.com/listing/467710794/personalized-natural-white-birch-wood?ref=shop_home_feat_1&amp;ep_click=1</description><guid isPermaLink="false">no</guid></item><item><title>Fern &amp; Garnet Necklace</title><link>https://www.etsy.com/listing/679524533/fern-garnet-necklace?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api</link><description>Handmade fern and garnet pendant! This is created with a real fern and deep red garnet. 

I love the deep, almost glow, of this garnet.


Made with love by Kimberly</description><guid isPermaLink="false">no</guid></item><item><title>Forbidden Forest candle, wizard candle, geeky fandom book candle, booklover gift,  soy candle scented, geeky candle</title><link>https://www.etsy.com/listing/496282967/forbidden-forest-candle-wizard-candle?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api</link><description>If you&amp;#39;re daring you might consider sneaking into the forbidden forest next to the hogwarts castle - but beware of the centaurs, they can&amp;#39;t take a joke! If you find a unicorn, only approach it if you&amp;#39;re female.. And if you love the scent of woods, pine trees and fresh air, give our Forbidden Forest candle a try! Notes of pine trees, mossy earth and damp leaves transport you right into the heart of the forbidden forest :)

Scent:
Pine needles, fresh air, wet leaves

Size: 6oz. of 100% pure soy wax. The jars are made of glass and each glass comes with a cork stopper. Each candle is carefully hand-poured in small batches; color and appearance may vary slightly from the photo. This listing is for one 180ml (6 oz) candle with a cork stopper and labelled as in the picture. If you have any questions or would like to request something custom-made, please contact me anytime!

Use: Soy wax burns nicely and cleanly and is eco-friendly! You&amp;#39;ll be able to clean out the jar and either recycle or reuse it. Burn time approx. 55 hours.

Shipping: Processing time for candles is about 7 days before they ship - please see my Shipping &amp; Policies page for current processing time before your order ships: https://www.etsy.com/shop/scentmeplaces/policy

My soy candles are made in Austria and poured in small batches - every candle is a unique one and there is a lot of work going into it. Every scent and color is tested for perfect scent throw and quality and I only sell candles and scents I am 100% sure about.

As I know that scents are a very personal matter, I am happy to accept returns if you don&amp;#39;t like the scent - if you&amp;#39;d rather prevent having to return a fragrance, you can try all our scents with our wax melts - just ask for one in a message!</description><guid isPermaLink="false">no</guid></item><item><title>Woodland Elf Costume For Women, Fairytale Outfit</title><link>https://www.etsy.com/listing/655946550/woodland-elf-costume-for-women-fairytale?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api</link><description>This amazing outfit was inspired by the vibes colors and feel of the forests surrounding before the winter hits up. 
Dark greens with a bit warmness of reddish and browns. 
This outfit is including a top, skirt, a headpiece and an arm art piece.

The base of the skirt is made of stretch velvet fabric, combined with layers of fur and asymmetrical fabric cuts so you can flip it and expose different parts of your figure, and wear it as it matches your body the most. 
I use a special bondage technique. Therefore, you can squeeze or release the top part of the skirt

The headdress is featured with feathers, chains, and beads, weightless on your head and will not slide down, look and feel amazing!

The armband art piece is adjustable to all sizes. 

Once you try this outfit, you will get hooked on this new comfort feeling, looks outstanding and also can be worn as a fairy tale costume, Halloween, or festival wear.

(If you want to change the length of the horns, contact me.)

*:*:* you’re welcome to choose the dress size, at the drop-down menu during checkout *:*:*

Available in sizes: XS-M US.
* Size XS US-
- Chest circumference: 76-80cm / 29.9-31.4’’
- Waist circumference: 62-66cm / 24.4-25.9’’ 
* Size S US-
- Chest circumference: 80-84cm / 31.4-33’’
- Waist circumference: 66-70cm / 25.9-27.5’’
Size M US-
- Chest circumference: 84-88cm / 33-34.6’’
- Waist circumference: 70-74cm / 27.5-29’’

I handmade this item by order, so I can change the details &amp; colors if you want; I need around 10 business days to finish it so please, order it ahead.

Don’t miss the opportunity to have your unique design at your next festival or your next Burning Man.
My designs are unique custom pieces, and each piece is one of a kind.

This listing includes: you’re welcome to choose at checkout;
* Brown-Beige skirt, made of Lycra &amp; Synthetic fur fabric, and chains as you can see in the listing photos.
* Brown Vest, made of Synthetic fur fabric
* Horn headpiece - 30cm / 11.8’’ long.

*ATTENTION*
This item is made to order, so I do not accept returns if you change your mind. Please think well and if you have any questions, feel free to contact me, I will be glad to help you.

*WASHING INSTRUCTIONS*
Hand washed in cold water and soap. Hang to dry in shade.

You’re welcome to see more of my designs here: https://etsy.me/2wOd3Mn

Much love!!
Yana</description><guid isPermaLink="false">no</guid></item><item><title>Forest Print, Wall Decor,Printable Art,Landscape Print,Wall Art,Forest Photography,Prints,Nature Print,Blue Green Poster,Art Print,Australia</title><link>https://www.etsy.com/listing/605603866/forest-print-wall-decorprintable?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api</link><description>Pine Forest Printable Wall Art #03

( Forest Print, Wall Decor,Printable Art,Landscape Print,Wall Art,Forest Photography,Prints,Nature Print,Blue Green Poster,Art Print,Australia )

This is an INSTANT DOWNLOAD of a photo of a mist filled Pine Forest. It looks fabulous on it&amp;#39;s own or in a nature themed gallery wall in your home.

Just print them on your home printer, or have the files printed by your local printing shop like Officeworks, Vista Print, Kmart, Target, Fedex or Costco (and grab frames while you&amp;#39;re here too), or upload them to an online printer like Snapfish, Mpix or Shutterfly and have then posted back to you.

These are all scaleable JPG files which means you can print them smaller or larger in full clarity and detail, up to the max size I&amp;#39;ve listed below for each ratio.

Please note this is a digital product for you to print. No physical prints or frame will be shipped. 

***WHAT YOU WILL RECEIVE***

1: Instructions file.

2: Printable art file of 2*3 ratio. These can be printed in the following sizes: 2*3, 4*6, 8*12, 12*18, 16*24, 20*30, 24*36 inches (up to 60cms by 90cms).

3: Printable art file of 3*4 ratio. These can be printed in the following sizes: 3*4, 6*8, 12*16, 24*32 inches (up to 60cms by 80cms)

4: Printable art file of 4*5 ratio.  These can be printed in the following sizes: 4*5, 8*10, 16*20, 24*30 inches (up to 60cms by 75cms).

5: Printable art file of standard International Paper Size, ie A1, A2, A3, A4, A5

6: Printable art file of 11*14 ratio.  These can be printed in the following sizes: 11*14 and 22*28 inches.

7: Printable art file of 5*7 ratio.  These can be printed in the following sizes: 5*7, 10*14, 15*21, 20*28 inches (up to 50cms by 70cms)

Each file is of a very high resolution at 300dpi (dots or pixels per inch). This simply means that they will look very sharp and clear no matter which of the listed sizes you print.

After checkout you will receive an email from Etsy with your order ready to download, as well as an instant link to download your files right from your checkout page. You can also access your downloadable files at any time through your Etsy purchase page.

Please visit the following Etsy link for help with Digital Downloads:

https://www.etsy.com/au/help/article/3949

Please note colours on different monitors may vary slightly and may be different again with each printer. 

All artwork copyright © 2018 Coastal Style Prints. Purchase is for personal use only. Strictly not for resale.

Thanks so much for stopping by,

Alice</description><guid isPermaLink="false">no</guid></item><item><title>Softie Sewing Pattern, fox sewing pattern, PDF Pattern, fox Plush, Plush Sewing Pattern, Felt sewing pattern, Forest Animal sewing pattern</title><link>https://www.etsy.com/listing/663077789/softie-sewing-pattern-fox-sewing-pattern?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api</link><description>Sew your own cute fox with this softie sewing pattern!

Meet Fez the Fox. Fez loves the forest, especially after sunset. He believes that’s when everyone and everything is at it’s most magical. He loves gazing at the moon and stars, but then again he also loves sitting around a campfire with his friends. “I just love the coziness” he always says. Tonight he plans to watch fireflies, and you’re definitely invited.

This plush sewing pattern is suitable for felt. The fox on the pictures is made out of 100% woolfelt.

This PDF pattern is a downloadable pattern. You can download this pattern immediately after payment.

Required materials:
• Orange, White, Black and Brown felt
• matching threads
• Regular (small eyed) needle
• Embroidery needle
• Scissors
• Sewing pins
• Printer &amp; copy paper
• Stuffing (fiberfill)

Skill Level: &amp;#39;Pretty&amp;#39; Easy!

The fox sewing pattern is full size, no scaling needed. Just print, cut, sew!
The finished fox measures 25x17 cm (10x6.7 inches) at widest points when finished.
If you want to make a different size fox, then just print the pattern out at a smaller percentage (80% 90% etc). 

This is a DIGITAL DOWNLOAD, not a PHYSICAL PRODUCT. You will not receive anything in the mail / by post. 

Available in English and Dutch.

Thank you for stopping by!

(◕‿◕)

a Dreamy Patterns design, Zerlina Slothouwer © 2018

Fox sewing pattern, Softie Sewing Pattern, PDF Pattern, fox Plush, Plush Sewing Pattern, Felt sewing pattern, Forest Animal sewing pattern</description><guid isPermaLink="false">no</guid></item><item><title>Serenity Letters. Watercolor floral alphabet clipart, leaf, monogram, gold, dusty green, wild, wedding, bridal, logo, diy, abc, greenery</title><link>https://www.etsy.com/listing/669211587/serenity-letters-watercolor-floral?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api</link><description>The Serenity Letters of 29 high quality golden uppercase Letters with leaves. Perfect graphic for branding, monograms, wedding invitations, greeting cards, photos, posters, quotes and more.
-----------------------------------------------------------------
This listing includes:
29 x Designed Letters, &amp;, +
All files in PNG with transparent background.
Height of symbol about 6in(17cm), 2400px, 300dpi, RGB
See the whole Serenity Collection: https://www.etsy.com/shop/OctopusArtis?search_query=serenity
-----------------------------------------------------------------
INSTANT DOWNLOAD
Once payment is cleared, you can download your files directly from your Etsy account.
----------------------------------------------------------------
PERSONAL USE
Personal Use is defined as using purchased Items in a manner that has no potential monetary gain. Personal Use projects cannot be related to any business, non-profit, or other organization of any kind. All purchased Items may be used in an unlimited number of Personal Use Projects.

COMMERCIAL USE
You may use the graphics as part of your products for sale. 
The graphics may not be used as is, in a stand alone fashion, but rather needs to form part of a new design that incorporates other resources, graphics and/or text.
For digital product the graphics that form part of the new design have to be flattened and uploaded as a background image where the graphics may not be extracted or moved or customized.

For small commercial use you are able to purchase the commercial license http://www.etsy.com/listing/222715263/

Do I need to purchase the License if I have shop on Etsy?
Not necessarily if you plan to sell ONLY in your shop on Etsy. But you MUST to give credit with link to our shop with the words:
&amp;quot;Graphics by OctopusArtis.etsy.com&amp;quot;.
Credit needs to be placed in your product description, on the same page as the product in an easily readable fashion.

----------------------------------------------------------------

Thanks for visiting our shop!
© Octopus Artis</description><guid isPermaLink="false">no</guid></item><item><title>Eucalyptus Wreaths &amp; Arrangements. Watercolor Floral clipart, leaves, leaf, greenery, green, wild, wedding, bridal, branch, forest, delicate</title><link>https://www.etsy.com/listing/653572940/eucalyptus-wreaths-arrangements?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api</link><description>Eucalyptus Wreaths &amp; Arrangements. The Floral Collection of 8 high quality hand painted watercolor Images. Perfect graphic for wedding invitations, greeting cards, photos, posters, quotes and more.
-----------------------------------------------------------------
This listing includes:
5 x Floral Wreaths
3 x Floral Arrangements
All files in PNG with transparent background.
Comes in different size, approx.: 13-10in(33-30cm), 4000-3600px, 300dpi, RGB
----------------------------------------------------------------
INSTANT DOWNLOAD
Once payment is cleared, you can download your files directly from your Etsy account.
-----------------------------------------------------------------
PERSONAL USE
Personal Use is defined as using purchased Items in a manner that has no potential monetary gain. Personal Use projects cannot be related to any business, non-profit, or other organization of any kind. All purchased Items may be used in an unlimited number of Personal Use Projects.

COMMERCIAL USE
You may use the graphics as part of your products for sale. 
The graphics may not be used as is, in a stand alone fashion, but rather needs to form part of a new design that incorporates other resources, graphics and/or text.
For digital product the graphics that form part of the new design have to be flattened and uploaded as a background image where the graphics may not be extracted or moved or customized.

For small commercial use you are able to purchase the commercial license http://www.etsy.com/listing/222715263/

Do I need to purchase the License if I have shop on Etsy?
Not necessarily if you plan to sell ONLY in your shop on Etsy. But you MUST to give credit with link to our shop with the words:
&amp;quot;Graphics by OctopusArtis.etsy.com&amp;quot;.
Credit needs to be placed in your product description, on the same page as the product in an easily readable fashion.
----------------------------------------------------------------

Thanks for visiting our shop!
© Octopus Artis</description><guid isPermaLink="false">no</guid></item><item><title>Eucalyptus Frames. Watercolor Floral clipart, leaves, leaf, greenery, green, wild, wedding, bridal, branch, forest, delicate, gentle, nature</title><link>https://www.etsy.com/listing/653553518/eucalyptus-frames-watercolor-floral?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api</link><description>Eucalyptus Frames. The Floral Collection of 7 high quality hand painted watercolor Frames. Perfect graphic for wedding invitations, greeting cards, photos, posters, quotes and more.
-----------------------------------------------------------------
This listing includes:
7 x Floral Frames
All files in PNG with transparent background.
Comes in different size, approx.: 13-10in(33-30cm), 4000-3600px, 300dpi, RGB
----------------------------------------------------------------
INSTANT DOWNLOAD
Once payment is cleared, you can download your files directly from your Etsy account.
-----------------------------------------------------------------
PERSONAL USE
Personal Use is defined as using purchased Items in a manner that has no potential monetary gain. Personal Use projects cannot be related to any business, non-profit, or other organization of any kind. All purchased Items may be used in an unlimited number of Personal Use Projects.

COMMERCIAL USE
You may use the graphics as part of your products for sale. 
The graphics may not be used as is, in a stand alone fashion, but rather needs to form part of a new design that incorporates other resources, graphics and/or text.
For digital product the graphics that form part of the new design have to be flattened and uploaded as a background image where the graphics may not be extracted or moved or customized.

For small commercial use you are able to purchase the commercial license http://www.etsy.com/listing/222715263/

Do I need to purchase the License if I have shop on Etsy?
Not necessarily if you plan to sell ONLY in your shop on Etsy. But you MUST to give credit with link to our shop with the words:
&amp;quot;Graphics by OctopusArtis.etsy.com&amp;quot;.
Credit needs to be placed in your product description, on the same page as the product in an easily readable fashion.
----------------------------------------------------------------

Thanks for visiting our shop!
© Octopus Artis</description><guid isPermaLink="false">no</guid></item><item><title>Vintage lumber Advertising from Forest City. PA</title><link>https://www.etsy.com/listing/603722238/vintage-lumber-advertising-from-forest?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api</link><description>Vintage Lumber Store Advertising &amp;quot;Another Bird Roof&amp;quot;

This framed Adverting piece is from a Lumber store in Forest City PA. It was in the location for many years. The pice has some damage around the corners which we have tried to show in the pictures. 
The piece measures:
Approx 25 inches tall
Approx 36.5 inches tall
Please feel free to email with any questions</description><guid isPermaLink="false">no</guid></item><item><title>Artistic Steel Driveway Gate - Woodland - Metal Wall Art - Handmade</title><link>https://www.etsy.com/listing/560969959/artistic-steel-driveway-gate-woodland?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api</link><description>Make every day a journey with the Woodlands decorative steel driveway gate.  An idyllic grove of trees plays home to cute furry and feathered friends, turning every trip to the store or return home into something out of a fairy tale.

Cut from 1/8th” steel sheeting, framed with 2″ steel tubing, each of our artisan gates are built to last for years of continuous use and exposure to the elements.

Although many of our competitors simply use paint, each of our artisan gates are primed and powder coated for protection from the elements while beautifully accenting your home or garden.  Powder coating typically produces a coating twice as thick as standard paint.  Powder coated surfaces are more resistant to chipping, scratching, and wearing than paint or other finishes.  The colors of your decorative steel gate will remain bright and vibrant over a longer period of time.  The result is a uniform, durable, high quality and attractive finish.

Our customers can customize their driveway gate with multiple powder coat color choices, designs, and sizing.  Artisan Gateworks standard steel driveway gates are built either 12’W x 6’H or 10’W x 6’H but we can make them in any size to fit your specifications.

**Note: As shown in the graphic, our standard sized driveway gates (as opposed to smaller, entryway gates)  are made from three panels framed with 2&amp;quot; square tube and separated by two 2&amp;quot; square tube dividers.  The photo of the Woodlands gate shown is a custom configuration with no dividing tubes, which may affect the price. Please contact us for details!**

All of our driveway gates are built without hardware, the customer will need to provide hardware specific to their needs or contact us for pricing and feasibility.

We love a challenge here at Artisan Gateworks, so please don’t hesitate to contact us for custom pieces if you have any ideas for the designs we have posted.

To see additional designs and to learn more about us, visit www.ArtisanGateworks.com

Our gates ship anywhere in the USA.


**TURNAROUND CAN VARY SIGNIFICANTLY FROM AS LITTLE AS TWO WEEKS TO 5 OR MORE WEEKS (although it&amp;#39;s rare that it&amp;#39;s that long). Be sure to email to ask for current turnaround if the timing is important to you.
---
**SHIPPING CHARGES LISTED ARE ONLY AN ESTIMATE, and vary by location; please email me for a shipping quote. We ship nationwide and local pick up is also available.

**Shipping will be quoted for &amp;quot;Standard Delivery&amp;quot; If you would like a quote on inside delivery, be sure to indicate that choice when requesting a quote.


***AGAIN, DO NOT RELY ON THE ETSY SHIPPING CALCULATOR, AS THOSE ARE ONLY AN ESTIMATE. PLEASE CONTACT US FOR A SHIPPING QUOTE.



* All rights reserved; Artisan Gateworks, LLC.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">no</guid></item><item><title>Autumn Sticker-Watercolour illustration tree seeds-decoration for Bulletjournal, school, university, planning, calendar</title><link>https://www.etsy.com/listing/625464420/autumn-sticker-watercolour-illustration?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api</link><description>These autumn stickers are perfect for beautifying everyday things, such as calendars (whether Carl, Filofax, Travellersnotebook or others), diary, letters, notebooks, gifts or the like. You can let your creativity run wild!

Because they are paper stickers that are not water repellent, they cannot be used outdoors.

Like all the stickers I sell in my shop, they are drawn, digitized, printed and plotted by me. They are handmade, so small color deviations as well as minimum size deviations are possible.


The DECO elements used for the presentation (brushes, paper clips, etc.) of the Stickerbogens are not included in the purchase price and are not sold.


If you have any questions, you can contact me! I will try to answer as soon as possible.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">no</guid></item><item><title>WOODLAND Nursery Wall Art Woodland Wall Art Wood Forest Animal Owl Deer Fox Bear Boy Bedroom Prints Set of 4</title><link>https://www.etsy.com/listing/463374528/woodland-nursery-wall-art-woodland-wall?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api</link><description>**THIS PRINT BACKGROUND COLOR CAN BE CUSTOM MADE TO DIFFERENT COLOR*


This adorable 4 piece print set would be a great addition to any forest-woodland nursery or playroom. 

Want to save 10% on your order? New Facebook followers receive 10% discount. Like our page to keep up with the latest news in the shop . Message me for your discount code!
https://www.facebook.com/KalasKorner

Follow us on Instagram #Kalaskorner

Each digitally created art piece is 8x10 and printed on premium photo paper.

With your print being printed on premium photo paper versus cardstock your prints will have rich and vibrant colors and last decades framed! .

I have other prints in my shop please stop in and take a look https://www.etsy.com/shop/KalasKorner


* please don&amp;#39;t hesitate to let me know if you would like me to make a custom print set for you at no extra charge. 

** PLEASE CARFULLY READ FULL DISCRIPTION OF PRODUCT BEFORE PURCHASE SO THERE IS NO CONFUSION ON THE PRODUCT YOU WILL RECIEVE***


** Prints are 8x10 

**Because of different computer monitor and phone screen settings colors may vary slightly. 

**My prints ARE NOT printed on canvas, I do not offer this option at this time

** Prints ARE NOT framed. 

** We ShIp Via FED EX EXPRESS to ensure quick and reliable shipping for our customers. If the address provided at check out is a PO BOX please provide a physical address for your order to be shipped to if you would like to utilize Fed Ex Express fast shipping. 

** We only ship products with in the U.S.A. sorry for any inconvenience. We do sell files to out of the country customers so they can print at home . 

** Because each print is made-to-order, returns/exchanges are not accepted. If for any reason you are unhappy with your order, please contact me directly before leaving a negative review. I would like the opportunity to resolve any issues you may have. I strive for 100% satisfaction with my customers


© Prettygrafik.com - etsy.com/shop/Prettygrafikdesign</description><guid isPermaLink="false">no</guid></item><item><title>Adventure Camping Fabric -  Kids Outdoors Bear Moose Arrow Print By Charlottewinter - White Navy Cotton Fabric By The Yard With Spoonflower</title><link>https://www.etsy.com/listing/594723216/adventure-camping-fabric-kids-outdoors?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api</link><description>woodland boys design mint grey navy blue bear moose forest arrow kids nursery baby print  designed by charlottewinter - Available printed onto the fabric type of your choice, for purchase by the yard -or- in Fat Quarter (1/4th yard) cuts. ◆PLEASE KEEP READING FOR DETAILS ABOUT OUR FABRIC AND CUT OPTIONS.◆

We digitally print each design onto a range of base fabrics, custom to order. We print using eco-friendly, water-based inks on natural and synthetic fiber textiles. No additional chemicals are used in the printing or preparation process.

All Spoonflower fabrics are printed in Durham, North Carolina, by a merry group of fabric lovers. All designs in our shop are crafted by independent surface designers who receive a commission on every sale. By ordering from Spoonflower, you help an independent designer earn a living!

++ For more information and fabric care instructions, please see our FAQs ++

◆◆◆CUT OPTIONS◆◆◆
-BY THE YARD: One yard of fabric measures 36 inches (91.44cm) in length. The width of a yard will depend on the type of fabric you choose, please scroll down to see the respective width for each fabric option. We do not offer half yards. We do not print on the selvedge.

**Multiple yards will print as a continuous length.**

-FAT QUARTER: A fat quarter is a quarter yard of fabric that measures 18 inches x half the width of fabric (a Basic Fat Quarter, for instance, would be a rectangle measuring 18&amp;quot; x 21&amp;quot;).

-SWATCH: Each of our sample swatches are 8x8 inches. Not sure what fabric type to choose or how the colors will look once printed? Order a sample swatch first!


◆◆◆FABRIC OPTIONS◆◆◆
You can have the design in the listing photos, custom printed onto your choice of the following fabrics:

Basic Cotton - 42” wide - $17.50/yard
- 100% combed cotton that is simple, lightweight, and easy to sew
- 3.2 oz per square yard (110 gsm)
- Estimated shrinkage: 2-4% in length and width
- Appropriate for basic craft projects, simple quilts, and bag liners.

Kona Cotton - 42&amp;quot; wide - $19/yard
- 100% natural combed cotton fabric with a wide weave that&amp;#39;s great for quilting
- 4.5 oz per square yard (155 gsm)
- Estimated shrinkage: 2-4% in length and 0-2% in width
- Appropriate for quilting, shirting, dresses, window treatments, nursery and home decor.

Cotton Poplin - 42” wide - $20/yard
- 100% natural cotton fabric with a fine weave and crisp, smooth feel
- 3.3 oz per square yard (115 gsm)
- Estimated shrinkage: 2-4% in length and width
- Appropriate for quilting, shirting, skirts, dresses, pajamas, and home decor.

Organic Cotton Knit - 56&amp;quot; wide - $27/yard
- 100% organic cotton knit fabric with a medium weight and cozy feel
- 6.3 oz per square yard (215 gsm)
- Estimated shrinkage: 9-11% in length and 5-7% in width.
- Interlock knit stretches along the crosswise grain about 25%.
- Certified organic cotton by Global Organic Textile Standards (GOTS)
- Appropriate for t-shirts, dresses, baby clothes, layettes, and blankets.

Organic Cotton Gauze - 56” wide - $23/yard
- 100% organic cotton double gauze fabric
- 3.5 oz per square yard (120 gsm)
- Estimated shrinkage: 8% width and 14% in length
- Appropriate for swaddle blankets, bibs, burp cloths, and reusable bags.
**Prints are likely to be off-grain. For softest feel, choose lightly colored designs.

Organic Cotton Sateen - 56&amp;quot; wide - $27/yard
- 100% organic cotton sateen with a subtle sheen and soft hand
- 3.8 oz per square yard (130 gsm)
- Certified organic cotton by Global Organic Textile Standards (GOTS)
- Estimated shrinkage: 2-4% in length and width
- Appropriate for quilting, curtains, table linens, bedding, clothing and pillows.

Cotton Spandex Jersey - 60” wide - $26.75/yard
- 93% natural cotton, 7% spandex jersey with a 4-way stretch
- 5.5 oz per square yard (185 gsm)
- Estimated shrinkage: 6-8% in length and 2-4% in width
- Appropriate for adult and baby apparel including loungewear, leggings, and t-shirts.

Linen Cotton Canvas - 54” wide - $27/yard
- 55% linen, 45% natural cotton fabric with a versatile medium weight and textured feel
- 6.4 oz per square yard (215 gsm)
- Estimated shrinkage: 2-4% in length and 0-2% in width
- Appropriate for curtains, tablecloths, tea towels, dresses, bags, and pillows.

Denim - 56&amp;quot; wide - $30/yard
- 100% natural cotton bull denim with a rugged twill construction
- 11.7 oz per square yard (395 gsm)
- Estimated shrinkage: 7-8% in length and 1-2% in width
- Perfect for skirts, shorts, pants, outerwear, bags and backpacks, and low-traffic upholstery

Cotton Canvas - 56&amp;quot; wide - $33/yard
- 100% natural cotton canvas with a sophisticated basketweave structure
- 10.6 oz per square yard (360 gsm)
- Estimated shrinkage: 3-4% in length and 0-1% in width
- Perfect for upholstery projects, heavyweight drapery, home accents and bags

Lightweight Cotton Twill - 58” wide - $26/yard
- 100% natural cotton twill fabric with a with a sturdy, drapable construction
- 5.8 oz per square yard (195 gsm)
- Estimated shrinkage: 4-6% in length and 1-2% in width
- Appropriate for home decor, drapery, table linens, pillows, tote bags, pants, coats and jackets.

Modern Jersey - 56” wide - $26.50/yard
- 995% polyester, 5% spandex jersey knit fabric with 4-way stretch and a cotton-like feel
- 6.2 oz per square yard (210 gsm)
- Estimated shrinkage: 4-6% in length and 2-4% in width
- Appropriate for t-shirts, tank tops, dresses, maxi skirts, headbands, scarves, and baby clothes.

Sport Lycra - 56” wide - $32/yard
- 88% polyester and 12% Lycra, moisture-wicking finish and 4-way stretch
- 8.5 oz per square yard (290 gsm)
- Estimated shrinkage: 0-2% in length and width
- Appropriate for athletic apparel, leggings, swimwear, yoga pants, and dance costumes.

Performance Piqué - 56&amp;quot; wide - $20/yard
- 100% polyester knit fabric with a diamond weave structure and a moisture-wicking finish
- 4.3 oz per square yard (145 gsm)
- Estimated shrinkage: 1-3% in length and 1-2% in width
- Perfect for yoga tops, polo shirts, sporty dresses and skirts, and headbands

Eco Canvas - 54” wide- $32/yard
- 100% polyester canvas with 45% recycled content
- 8.1 oz per square yard (275 gsm)
- Estimated shrinkage: 0-2% in length and width
- Appropriate for upholstery, bags, home decor, outdoor pillows, toys, play mats, and jackets.

Velvet - 54” wide - $34/yard
- 100% polyester velvet fabric with a short pile and subtle shimmer
- 10.9 oz per square yard (370 gsm)
- Estimated shrinkage: 5-6% in length and 2-3% in width
- Perfect for home decor and commercial-grade upholstery, heavyweight apparel, and luxurious accessories

Satin - 54&amp;quot; wide - $20/yard
- 100% polyester satin fabric with a silky feel and high-gloss finish
- 2.2 oz per square yard (75 gsm)
- Estimated shrinkage: 1-2% in length and 0-1% in width
- Perfect for lining apparel and bags, wedding decor, and soft, silky accessories

Chiffon - 54&amp;quot; wide - $21/yard
- 100% polyester chiffon fabric with a translucent look and delicate drape
- 1.5 oz per square yard (50 gsm)
- Estimated shrinkage: 0-1% in length and width
- Perfect for scarves, sheer curtains, and special occasion decor items

Minky - 54” wide - $27/yard
- 100% polyester minky fabric with a soft, napped finish for the ultimate in plush
- 6.6 oz per square yard (225 gsm)
- Estimated shrinkage: 2-4% in width and 0-2% in length
- Appropriate for quilting, blankets, lounge wear, plushies, and cold weather accessories.

Fleece - 56” wide - $27/yard
- 100% polyester low-loft fleece fabric with a slight stretch and soft, cuddly feel
- 6.6 oz per square yard (225 gsm)
- Estimated shrinkage: 1-2% in width and length
- Appropriate for cozy loungewear, pillows, and blankets (including no-sew tie blankets)


When it comes to colors, every fabric base will present a color quite differently. This can be due to a number of factors, including fiber type, fabric weave, absorbency and printing method. Polyester fabrics tend to present color more vibrantly and offer a more crisp print compared to natural fibers (cotton, linen, etc). </description><guid isPermaLink="false">no</guid></item><item><title>Ladies Hope Love Cure Support Uterine Cancer Awareness Moisture Wicking V-neck Long Sleeve Tee T-Shirt HLC-SUCA-LST353LS</title><link>https://www.etsy.com/listing/560969533/ladies-hope-love-cure-support-uterine?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api</link><description>This ladies fitness moisture wicking v-neck long sleeve shirt is featuring Hope Love Cure Support Uterine Cancer Awareness!


Lightweight, roomy and highly breathable, these moisture-wicking, value-priced tees feature PosiCharge technology to lock in color and prevent logos from fading.

3.8-ounce, 100% polyester interlock with PosiCharge technology
Gently contoured silhouette
Removable tag for comfort and relabeling
Self-fabric v-neck
Set-in sleeves

All items are hand pressed and printed to order in beautiful Clermont, FL!

~Tag us and post a picture of you wearing this shirt on Instagram and receive a $5 discount on your next order~ @Buycoolshirts



Returns/Exchange Form:
If you suspect the product is defective or an incorrect item has been sent, please email us first.

Care Information:
Wash inside out and use cold water. Do NOT use bleach or iron over the decal.

Return Policy:
If you are not 100% satisfied with your purchase you may return it for a full refund of the original purchase price (SHIPPING NOT INCLUDED). We must receive the unworn product 30 days from the date the item is delivered. Items that are damaged/stained in any way, smell like smoke, are covered in pet/human hair or have the size label/tag cut or torn out are not returnable under any circumstances.

Please be sure to return a copy of your packing slip or the original. Your order ID number is required for processing your exchange/refund. You may want to make a copy for your records.

Refunds will be issued to the credit card or PayPal account used to make the purchase. Please keep in mind that credit card refunds can take anywhere up to 5 business days to post on the account once the refund has been processed.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">no</guid></item><item><title>Bigfoot likes icecream</title><link>https://www.etsy.com/listing/647650359/bigfoot-likes-icecream?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api</link><description>A print of an original watercolor painting 
This comes two sizes; 11 x 14 inches and 8 x 10 inches.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">no</guid></item><item><title>Harness lingerie set, Black lingerie, Red wine harness, Purple lingerie, Deep forest lingerie, Sissy lingerie, Bondage gear</title><link>https://www.etsy.com/listing/676070533/harness-lingerie-set-black-lingerie-red?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api</link><description>You acquire: bra + panties 

If you looking for sexy lingerie that will add some spice to your relationship - this one is definitely a good choice. Pretty and sexy bralette and panties.
Made from not elastic lace and black elastic ribbon. Almost all the strappy are adjustable, so this harness set is ideal for your body. The beautifull lines of those pieces will highlight the most beautiful and feminine parts of your body. All metal details are in silver color. 
This BDSM lingerie I can sew in different colors:
* black strappy + purple ink lace
* black strappy + dusty cherry lace
* black strappy + deep forest lace

PRODUCT DETAILS
* triangle cups
* not have wire
* not padding
* adjustable shoulder straps
* adjustable back closure
* metal sliders

You can personalize your order:
* I can sew this harness set for you from the lace of another color.
* I can sew this harness set for you with your measurements.

Also you can purchase any item from this underwear separately.

Please do not hesitate to write messages and ask questions.

More designs: https://www.etsy.com/shop/BlossomBody

♡For XS size: 
Bust = 32,5 inches / 82 cm 
Waist = 25,5 inches / 64 cm 
Hips = 34,5 inches / 88 cm

♡For S size: 
Bust = 34,5 inches / 88 cm 
Waist = 27,5 inches / 70 cm 
Hips = 37 inches / 94 cm

♡For M size: 
Bust = 37 inches / 94 cm 
Waist = 30 inches / 76 cm 
Hips = 39,5 inches / 100 cm

♡For L size: 
Bust = 39,5 inches / 100 cm 
Waist = 32,5 inches / 82 cm 
Hips = 41,5 inches / 106 cm

♡For XL size: 
Bust = 41,5 inches / 106 cm 
Waist = 34,5 inches / 88 cm 
Hips = 44 inches / 112 cm

If your size is not available in this listing, just send me your measurements after the purchas. Please do not hesitate to ask questions.

♡ made for you ♡
Made in Ukraine (Cherkasy city)

More designs: https://www.etsy.com/shop/BlossomBody</description><guid isPermaLink="false">no</guid></item><item><title>Forest at Dusk</title><link>https://www.etsy.com/listing/632693244/forest-at-dusk?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api</link><description>Title: Forest at Dusk
Direct from my studio in Birmingham, AL
This listing: Original Painting + Framed + Ready to hang
Size (artwork framed): 11&amp;quot; x 14&amp;quot; -- ITEMS SHIPS FRAMED! 
Size (artwork): 5.75&amp;quot; x 8.75&amp;quot;
Materials used: acrylic ink, graphite pencil, India ink, acid-free paper

Frame: Black + Ready to hang!

________________________________________

When you support a small business, you&amp;#39;re supporting a dream ---- THANK YOU for checking out my shop! 
Be sure to favorite!

________________________________________

All Rights and licenses are reserved for Amanda Klein at MandaMakesArt. Images cannot be copied or used without license agreement from artist. Copyrights apply international and violators will be prosecuted.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">no</guid></item><item><title>One Pine Tree Wall Decal - Pine Forest Wall Art - Vinyl Christmas Tree Sticker Home Decor  - K474</title><link>https://www.etsy.com/listing/679523959/one-pine-tree-wall-decal-pine-forest?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api</link><description>ONE Pine Tree Wall Decal / Pine Forest Wall Sticker for home or office. Wall art decal features five pine tree of different size.

Design K474 - One Pine Tree Wall Decal (2 size options)

♥  P R O D U C T  - D I M E N S I O N S  ♥
Two options are available.
K474S: 15&amp;quot;w x 50&amp;quot;h
K474L: 20&amp;quot;w x 67&amp;quot;h

♥  D E C A L -  M A T E R I A L S  ♥
We use high-quality commercial-grade removable wall decal which creates a beautiful paint-like look on your wall once applied. They can be used on walls (including slightly textured walls, except sandy and grainy), mirrors, doors, windows, and furniture. Our decals are removable and will not damage your walls. They are easy to apply and will instantly transform a blank and boring wall into a lively and lovely scene!

♥  W H A T &amp;#39; S -  I N C L U D E D  ♥
Decal set includes: 1 pine tree. Assembly is required.
Detailed step-by-step installation instructions.
1 small test decal.
1 applicator tool.
50&amp;quot;h is cut in 1 piece. 67&amp;quot; tree is cut into two pieces which require assembly.

♥  C H O O S I N G  - C O L O R S  ♥
Choose 1 color from our color chart to replace default color of dark grey.
Please enter your request for custom color in the &amp;quot;message to seller&amp;quot; box when you check out.  If no color is chosen, we will cut your design in default colors listed above.

♥  C U S T O M I Z I N G -  Y O U R -  D E S I G N  ♥
- We can size up or down your design, or use additional colors. Please contact us for pricing!
- We can do a reverse cut at no extra charge. Simply leave a note when you check out.

♥  I N S T A L L I N G -  O U R -  D E C A L S  ♥
Detailed step-by-step instructions, one applicator tool, and one small test decal are included with every order. Larger decals come pre-masked with transfer paper; please note certain elements may require cutting apart before applying to the wall. Smaller decals do not require masking and can be applied like traditional stickers (just peel and stick). Our decals are removable, so you can easily reposition small pieces to create a perfect look.

Note that not all surfaces are suitable for vinyl decal application. Please read ALL of our policies page prior to purchase to learn about surface and paint issues that could affect vinyl application:
http://www.etsy.com/shop/stampmagick/policy

See more of our wall decal designs at http://www.etsy.com/shop/stampmagick

© 2019 StampMagick</description><guid isPermaLink="false">no</guid></item><item><title>Vinyl Sticker Love Birds Tree Branches Floral Ornament Swallows Forest Doves Poster Kids Room Baby Nursery Mural Decal Wall Art Decor ZX2234</title><link>https://www.etsy.com/listing/679523843/vinyl-sticker-love-birds-tree-branches?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api</link><description>The new generation of home improvement product presented in our goods, which you can pick and choose. Ready and easy to apply and remove any time, quick way to decorate your place and create a unique atmosphere in your home! Great present for your friends and the loved ones from the variety on any taste and color! Welcome to the future!</description><guid isPermaLink="false">no</guid></item><item><title>Scandinavian Poster, Abstrack Print, Forest Poster, Pine Tree Art, Geometric Print, Printable Art</title><link>https://www.etsy.com/listing/652071297/scandinavian-poster-abstrack-print?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api</link><description>Join my mailing list today to get instant 10% off on Your first purchase and also to be the first to hear about new collections, awesome sales and special offers!

----------------------------------------https://bit.ly/2wMTaUR-------------------------------------------

Hi, Welcome to my shop! Thank you for your interest, If you have any questions regarding my digital prints or photographs please feel free to contact me.

Details: 

Scandinavian Abstract Print

I N C L U D E D - F I L E S

A 1x1 ratio file for printing: 8&amp;quot;x8&amp;quot; / 20x20 cm, 12&amp;quot;x12&amp;quot; / 30x30 cm , 16&amp;quot;x16&amp;quot; / 40x40 cm, 24&amp;quot;x24&amp;quot; / 60x60 
A 2x3 ratio file for printing 6&amp;quot;x9&amp;quot; / 15x23 cm, 8&amp;quot;x12&amp;quot; / 20x30 cm, 10&amp;quot;x15&amp;quot; / 25x40 cm, 12&amp;quot;x18&amp;quot; / 30x45 cm, 16&amp;quot;x24&amp;quot; / 40x60 cm
A 3x4 ratio file for printing 6&amp;quot;x8&amp;quot; /15x20 cm, 9&amp;quot;x12&amp;quot; / 23x30 cm, 12&amp;quot;x16&amp;quot; / 30x40 cm, 18&amp;quot;x24&amp;quot; / 45x60 cm
A 4x5 ratio file for printing 8&amp;quot;x10&amp;quot; / 20x25 cm, 16&amp;quot;x20&amp;quot; / 40x50 cm


I N S T A N T - D O W N L O A D

Please Note that this item is a digital download, no physical product will be shipped.

Purchasing a digital print is an affordable way to decorate your home or office since there are no shipping and packing fees! You can download and print it immediately on any kind of paper you like.

If you don&amp;#39;t want to bother with printing and would like to receive a printed version, please visit this link:

https://etsy.me/2JItSNG

For other digital prints look around here: https://etsy.me/2ISAb0A

To look around in my shop visit this link: https://etsy.me/2zHFMo8

Please take into consideration that due to different monitor/printer setting the color may differ.
Please note that any blur, out of focus or texture on my images are intentional.


This purchase is for PERSONAL USE ONLY!
 © All Artwork is copyright of InShoesOfM 


Thank you for visiting!</description><guid isPermaLink="false">no</guid></item></channel></rss>